(phone ringing)
- They don't want it.
I'll put it on like that.
(upbeat music)
- Hi, Andy.
- Hello, Andy.
- Welcome to "Droppers of Line", everybody.
Welcome to our audience feedback show,
whether you're watching, whether you're listening,
whether you're performing.
- Performing, welcome to you.
- Welcome to you, Andy.
- Thank you.
No one has ever welcomed me to "Droppers of Line".
- Ah, is that what you've wanted?
- No.
- I don't want it.
- Oh, I take it back now.
- Oh, no.
Oh, well.
Hey, Ho, it was nice while it lasted.
- What would you like to start with?
Can you do that? - Can you do that off the hook?
- Get yourself off the hook.
That's so weird.
It's first in my notes.
- That's 'cause it's first every time.
- Yep.
- Well, we can mix it up.
- No, no, no.
We love it.
- All right.
- And we love you.
- Okay, right.
Let's just clear the elephant in the room.
These guys are being nice to me
because we've had a lot of emails saying,
Andy, I hope you're all right.
Just want to let you know.
Don't let the bullying get to you on the show.
- What are you on about?
- What, oh, that's exactly what a bully would do though, isn't it?
- No.
- Ghost you.
- People are saying, no, it's just like people are saying,
oh, Andy, everyone's giving you a really hard time
about the brilliant and unstructured way.
You host things or, you know, your funny names
which you think had named for one reason
with the actually named after someone with a funny name.
You know, and people are just thinking,
oh, I'm being piled on a lot at the moment.
I actually disagree.
I think it works perfectly.
- Yeah.
- A bit of me that's interested in making a damn good show.
Things we need hero and a villain.
- That's the only reason why we're doing it.
- It's the only reason why we're doing it.
- It's the only reason you're doing it.
- The other reason that I'm doing what?
(laughing)
And that's what he does.
He gets in your head.
- Right.
- No, can we just say, for context, we're all friends, right?
- We're all colleagues.
- We're all friends, and we do this.
That's the joke, right?
- If I presented increase in chaos
and you guys just merrily went along with it,
I think the joke would lose a little of its picolcy.
- Let's give it a go.
(laughing)
- We're gonna be unfunny as droppers like we've ever done,
'cause you guys are just going,
great format point, Andy.
Oh, well, really fun.
No, no, no, no, come on, bring it on.
Get yourself off the hook.
- Love it.
- 'Cause I'm gonna be getting you on the hook.
So you know. - Thank you.
- Right.
Okay, a couple of things about Cheeksall and Boxes.
- Oh, great, yeah.
- So we said on the show that,
or someone wrote in to say,
you never get 1,000 piece Cheeksall.
And I said that I have evidence
that you can sometimes get 1,000 piece Cheeksall.
- Yes.
- I'm speaking you don't because of the format of a box.
- The puzzles dimensions have to match the box.
The puzzle has to match the picture on the box
and the box can't be done in the right size.
- Have we got the role for eternity of dysectologists?
(laughing)
- We haven't, sadly.
We've got Jim here, son, though, and you're very welcome, Jim.
Saying, why does the puzzles dimensions have to match the box?
Surely you could just fit a 20 by 50 thing
on a standard box, which will be 1,000 pieces,
and the blank space above and below the image
could be used for labeling in such like.
- They're labeling such like, yeah, fair enough.
- It would help the word stand out more
and wouldn't obscure the image.
Feels like a win-win to me, says Jim.
(laughing)
- I know what you mean.
I think they want the image to be as large
as possible on the box, 'cause that's what sells it.
- Yeah.
- And it's what helps you when you're doing the Jigsaw as well.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But no, it's a clever idea.
- Yeah.
- I look forward to you implementing this, Jim.
- I just still think it's mad that we're trying to work
for the Jigsaw people, and there's not just a big set
of emails going, yeah, what's up with the box
from a monopoly going on here, where they're refusing
to change sizes, yeah.
- Yeah, but the box works for all the different companies.
They're not beholden to whatever the Jigsaw people want.
The box people are making stuff for all different games.
- That's true, but they do make different sizes of box, don't they?
They should be able to, like, I've seen,
I've got Jigsaws which have different size boxes.
- How do you?
- Yeah, I'm just doing all right for myself.
- How many have you got?
They're a few knocking about, we should come around,
we should have a game's night, a game's night, a Jigsaw night.
- Yeah.
- Is that a game?
- It feels just like time-killing to me, a Jigsaw.
- Well, he just said that we should hang out outside of work.
- Do you see why it's so hard to be your friend?
- That's what a bully would say.
- You forced me to bully, suggesting a game's night
at your hand, oh, the game, unbelievable.
- Okay, okay, we'll have a Jigsaw night, all right?
- The game's night.
- Okay, what game are we playing?
- Jigsaw, game, we've been Jigsaw.
- It's a game, it's a past time.
- How do you win?
- It's a past time.
- Two Jigsaws, first person to complete their Jigsaw.
- Oh, that is a bit of a tournament now, wow.
- It's a game.
- Okay.
- Sorry to have angered you by pushing back quite gently
at the or idea that we'd gamified the Jigsaw.
- I did not think this is how we'd fall out, but here we are.
- It's got a lot of edge to it, this Jigsaw tab.
- Right, I'm actually, that was the serious get yourself off the hook.
Now we're in, I'm actually, which is lighter points of correction.
- Okay.
- It's not quite good, isn't it?
That was the heaviest thing we've got corrected all this week.
- That's good.
- I'm actually, oh, this is an important point,
because we're recording a show tonight,
which will mention the nobels at the Royal Institution.
Listening to episode 617 says Madeline Christensen,
and you hit on a pet peeve of mine.
You do not win a Nobel Prize.
It is awarded.
You're not a Nobel Prize winner, you are a laureate.
It is not a contest race or a lottery.
Madeline sounds like she has opinions of whether a Jigsaw is a game or not.
Maybe it's because I am Swedish, this bugs me.
- Really?
- Interesting.
Okay, hang on.
So there's a bunch of people nominated.
They then pick the person.
Is that still not a committee awarding?
- Not being judged.
- Yeah.
- It is awarded.
- Is it a semantic thing, as in they deliberately say it's not a winning thing
because they don't want people to think that it's competition or...
- Madeline doesn't even say that they don't say it is.
It just seems to be a thing that it's just a terminological thing.
- You're just pretty naged.
- You're just...
- Your name...
- It's awarded to you and you then become a laureate, not a winner.
And I do actually have a bit in the show about why you shouldn't celebrate
brashly winning.
So I'll save that for later.
- Okay.
- Exciting.
- I think that one is in "Not Tonight" show, but tomorrow's show.
- Oh dear.
(laughing)
- Well, I've got to come search a different show.
Let's battle through.
Andy and Miko, the dog.
- Hi, guys, love the program. Always listen when walking our pooch.
- This is Andy writing.
- Yeah, it's a joke.
(laughing)
- Otherwise, it's a very unusual nickname that Miko, the dog has for his owner.
- PS, love pissing on trees.
(laughing)
In a recent episode, you were talking about hair nets.
I remember visiting a...
(laughing)
- I've miscategorized this.
This is bonus brain, not an arm actually.
- Okay.
- Have you played one?
- Yeah, yeah.
- On my board.
- I remember visiting a museum in Pompeii, I think it was,
where there is a solid gold hair net on display, so finely made.
This type of hair net must be a contender for the most expensive hair net.
- Yeah.
- But as far as I'm aware, there haven't been sold at auction.
- That's so true.
- How did a gold hair net survive the total destruction of Pompeii?
- Yes.
- That feels implausible, doesn't it?
- Metal.
- Might have survived.
- It's old.
- Yeah.
- Might have been buried under something else.
- Feels like one of the last things I'd expect to survive.
- Yeah.
- Maybe someone put it on, hoping it would, like, do something against the pyroclastic flow.
- That'll be it.
- That'll be it, yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
Well, that's a great fact, Andy, and fair play.
- And a good Orozco.
I think James said in a recent episode that humans are the only animals who could actively
control their defecation.
- I did say that.
- But who's some folds in Uranus.
- But folds in Uranus.
Yeah, yeah.
But surely his Evian drinking cat doesn't just shed her soul forever, she happens to be
at the moment.
That's true for most dogs as well.
- Yeah.
- She doesn't hold it in for hours if she's like in a queue or something.
Like, she will, I mean, if she needs to go, she just goes.
- But there's limited control, like some animals have limited control where they can scratch
at the door.
- I think that's what I'm saying.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Just to follow it, finish Anna's email.
Furthermore, I know it's a bit of a cliché by now to say, surely you've received hundreds
of emails saying this, but I strongly believe it to be true.
I missed the section, naming section in the last drop of the line, and I loved the things
that are not named after what you think they're named after.
Please fight for them.
I know you have the numbers behind you.
- It's just literally copy-pasted.
I reckon there's some forums somewhere that says, if you want to get mentioned on the drop
of the line, just copy-paste this paragraph and Andy guarantees to get you in.
- It has a correction about hardwood as well.
- Oh, okay.
- We've said eucalyptus trees.
- Eucalyptus trees.
- Eucalyptus, we've said it is a softwood or a hardwood.
We've had a lot of corrections about it.
- Are they corrections of the correction because we've already done a correction?
- Yeah, they are unfortunately.
- Wow.
- Serum of cold points out hardness is not to do with the hardness of the wood.
This is a botanical term, which is just about the kind of tree it is.
- Okay.
- So, balsa wood is technically a hardwood, even though it's very soft.
- Which we've done on QI.
- Jeremy Verm, French Jeremy Fight, is a wood sculptor and Richard wrote in with a brilliant
quite a long explanation.
We don't have time for the whole thing, but hardwoods are angiosperms and softwoods are
gymnosperms and it's about whether they flower or not and it's just slightly different.
There's a hardness scale called the jankous scale.
- Anna said Eucalyptus was a softwood.
Someone wrote in saying, "No, it's a hardwood."
- And then we said something about whether it's hard or not.
- Oh, did we?
- It's one of those things that I think is a third rail that you shouldn't touch.
- Okay.
- There's no one allowed to mention any trees for the rest of the tummy-makers show.
- You know?
It's just, that's too much.
- Matt Underwood writes about stopping smoking.
- We're not talking about wood anymore Andy.
- Very good.
We'll move on.
- No, we came up with different ways of stopping smoking.
- Yeah.
- And Matt has a great bonus fact.
Matt writes, "I should tell you about my dad.
Dad was a heavy smoker for 20 odd years.
Then in the mid-90s he was knocked down by a car and had quite a serious head injury.
One of the side effects was that he had amnesia and forgot among other things that he
smoked.
- Oh.
- The family chose not to remind him and he is still a non-smoker 30 years later.
- If he listens to this episode, is he going to revamp that?
- I wrote it and checked and Matt said, "Yeah, it doesn't matter, go for it."
Although very effective, I would not necessarily recommend this as a treatment.
My mum lives in fear that he'll get a second blow to the head and this thing is memory.
- That's, that's something, isn't it?
- That's incredible.
- That's just, yeah.
- It doesn't feel, it doesn't feel, I know.
- But it will feel like you'd have a nicotine memory.
You'd have, your fingers would have tobacco stains on them or whatever and you'd want to smoke.
- And it feels like your whole life would be having to run ahead of your dad if you see
an old friend in the distance to remind them not to offer a cigarette to him.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's your whole life is just, oh my god, I can't believe it.
- But he might just say, "No, I'm alright, I got to smoke."
- You don't smoke.
- Yeah.
- You just smoke 90 and do all the photos around the house with a cigarette.
- You just start to shut them out, don't you?
Is it Disney?
- Well Disney, yeah.
- All the photos around Disney were just in point to get things now.
- Yeah, yeah, because it was like Donald Duck bonked him on the head with a huge handle.
- Matt does say PS, he's fine, so it's okay to laugh.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, do you?
That's very funny.
- I know.
- Mattias Lundberg writes about cabbages and condoms, which you covered when I was not here.
- Yeah, so this was a restaurant in Thailand and it's condom theme, but it had a sort of purpose
behind it to educate.
- Yeah, the idea is that asking for condoms should be just as normal as asking for cabbages.
- Yeah.
And Mattias just provides a little extra bonus beam about this, which is that there's a doctor
called Dr. Metchai Viravidea, who, beginning in the 70s, promoted condom use for family planning,
and then during the HIV/AIDS crisis to prevent transmission, he would dress up as a large condom
and hand condoms out to people on the streets.
- Nice, nice.
- And he almost single-handedly brought down both fertility and HIV transmission.
- Yeah, really cool.
- It's great.
- It's such a great idea.
- Very cool.
- We've got to play on.
We've got to play on.
That's plow.
This is crazy.
Martin Hoven has an email about something that he doesn't know we've already talked about,
but in a show that hasn't gone out yet.
- Wow.
- So I love this when this happens.
- Yeah.
- Do you remember we talked about Clarence Saunders?
- Yes.
- Who started the grocery shop.
- Bigly wiggly.
- Bigly wiggly in 1916.
And it was the first one where you could get the stuff off the thing.
- Martin has found a fact that we didn't do.
- Oh, great.
- But it's so good.
- So this will have gone out by the time this goes out, but at the time of recording, it hasn't
gone out.
- Yeah.
- So don't put this out early.
Guys, if that's all right.
- Don't put this out early.
- Don't put this out early because then that'll pre-empt the episode with the
bigly wiggly stuff in it.
- Don't worry.
I'm not rushing this one out.
- But you might find a good day to bury bad news.
Like if something awful happens in the news, you might think that's a good time to slip out
that.
- No one will notice it.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
That's a good point.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Anyway.
Clarence Saunders.
- Which you put all the episodes of Drop of the Lied Out when something really bad has
happened.
- Yeah.
- You think that's why the news has been so bad over the last two or three years.
They're just doing it the other way round.
They're like, "Oh, Drop of the Lied is coming out.
We better do something terrible."
Stop people from listening to it.
- It's a big campaign to stop this being the biggest show in Britain.
- It's working.
- Do you all know the answer to this?
But James, when do you think we did our first Drop of the Lied out?
- A couple of years ago, I guess.
- Yeah.
- So what?
- 2026, 2024.
- Okay.
As far as I can tell, we started this in like May 2022.
- Yep.
- Wow.
- Is that right?
- Yep.
- And I think I said this before recently the first one we put out was 17 minutes long.
- Yeah.
- And I think we used everything we had.
Whereas you don't know.
We've recorded two hours for this.
- Yeah.
- You're seeing only the finest cream in that dream.
- That's amazing.
- There's so many crazies in 2022.
- I know.
Four years we've been doing Drops of the Lied.
- But it hasn't felt like that to me.
- If it was a child, it'd be going to primary school now.
- Yes.
- Wow.
- But as it is, it's learned nothing.
(laughing)
- And we've taken a photo of it in some school uniform and then put it out on Facebook
and telling everyone how beautiful it looks.
- As it is, it's been banned from every school in the area.
- Yeah.
- Like all the schools we've applied to have said no.
We don't want a couple of Lied in our school.
It's bad influence.
(laughing)
- It's gonna have to be home-schooled.
- Yeah.
- There's a serious bullying problem here.
(laughing)
- Clarence Saunders.
- Yeah.
- Pickley Wiggly.
- Pickley Wiggly lost control of his company.
But he started again.
He had a new chain and he'd modernized it even more.
Like there were even more bits that were kind of automated or, you know, where there wasn't
a clerk.
He had to handle it.
- Yeah.
- Trump left too.
But before he launched it, the new owners took him to court on the grounds that the name Clarence
Saunders in relation to a grocery chain infringed on their trademark because they had
bought Pickley Wiggly.
- Oh.
- You're saying your own name is associated with Pickley Wiggly then for you to reach.
- Yeah.
- So he named his store, the Clarence Saunders sole owner of my name store.
- Oh.
- That was the name of the store.
- Wow.
- Clarence Saunders sole owner of my name.
And he then, and they were a huge success.
- Wow.
- And then he bought, he founded a professional American football team, which he named the Clarence
Saunders sole owner of my name, Tigers.
- That's crazy.
- Who does that want a hero?
- Anyway, that's a great story.
Thank you, Mark.
- Incredible story.
- Yeah.
- That was, Hank Green covered that recently.
He's a friend of the podcast, isn't he?
Full guest?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Brilliant.
Fish life.
- Fish life.
Brilliant.
- Where's Stone writes with a very good bit of fish life.
- Yeah.
- Any of you remember, effect Anna brought about sardines a few years ago.
She claimed rotating cans of sardines helps develop their flavor.
- Oh, I do remember that, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Well, after hearing the pod, I went to Portugal and brought back some sardines.
- For the past two and a half years, I've been turning the cans every couple of months.
- Charlie, this deserves to be an extreme fish, Andy.
- And I've recently cracked them open to see if they were any better than the control
tins of sardines I bought.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Fair good.
- Well, that was true scientist.
- This guy, Wes, you're about after my own heart.
When I announced the good news that we would finally be eating the sardines, my wife, that's
the most surprising part of it so far.
- My wife said, "Fantastic, I'm really looking forward to you not telling me about the sardines
anymore."
I told you two years ago that I didn't like them.
With her endorsement, I was excited to give them a go.
I can report back that there was no difference between the turncans and the control.
- Interesting.
- Yeah.
- I think it's really important in science if you get a no result that you still report it.
- Yeah, true.
- Yeah, so true.
This Wes is clearly a scientist of some kind.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
So anyway, wonderful.
Thank you, Wes.
- Yeah.
- Wes, as well.
- The real hero of that story.
- Absolutely.
- I'm sticking with Wes.
- I wonder how many people at home right now listening to this are a year and a half into
their experiment with the sardines.
- Oh, great.
- Having the tail.
- Sike.
- I think, okay, I'm getting an insight into this marriage.
I think that Mrs. Wes has been secretly turning both cows into a smileless experiment.
- Wes doesn't know, he's playing with all fantastic all that's so tragic.
Oh, dear.
- Wonderful.
Metahalba, from Norway, thanks to you beautiful people, I've made quite an impression on
my new colleague.
I started a new job in January and was excited by my colleague ask if I wanted to come
with her to a pub quiz.
We did pretty well on the first rounds, but the last question on the quiz was, what
did, now there's a slight error in here, so just brace for that.
What did Benjamin Franklin invent that saved President Garfield's life?
I think we mean Alexander Graham, right?
- Yeah.
- And it didn't really save his life.
- Exactly.
Yeah.
I said, it has to be tube feeding through the anus.
- Is it a pub quiz scenario?
It was wrong.
- It was a metal detector.
Which we did say in the show, you've just remembered the wrong bit.
- Yeah.
- Absolutely.
- Or is this bonus beam?
Was Ben Franklin there with a tube?
- Absolutely.
150 years populous.
- Yes.
- But.
- Oh my god, it's the ghost of Benjamin Franklin.
What's he doing with that tube?
- Every wrestling match should be Benjamin Franklin coming up with a tube.
He's trying to stick out of the place.
- Oh, great.
Right.
- Thanks.
But no thanks.
- Oh yeah.
- James Patterson, brackets, not the author, both brackets.
I joined the Dennis the Menace fan club in the early 1980s.
- Yeah.
- Cool, says James.
Members have a secret code phrase to identify each other.
- I know it.
- Unfortunately, club rules forbid me from discussing the matter further.
So, you know, but that's cool that you and James both know it.
- Yeah.
We have a siege other we can do it.
- Exactly.
But it got me thinking that club fish could introduce a code.
So, members could identify each other.
Perhaps using the phrase, this ass eats.
- Okay.
Well, the idea is that one of you says part of a code,
and then you say it, but it sounds just normal.
Like, if people are walking past,
they would think you're just being normal.
Then the other person says the second half of the code,
and you know that you're in the same gang.
- Right.
- So it's like spies, you know, the red owl is flying in.
- So you'd like, what pass someone in the past?
You'd go, this ass.
And then they would go, "Eats."
That was what James said.
- Yeah, there we go.
- So, because that's how it does.
The menu's where it works, right?
But I do wonder if this ass is a little bit...
- Provoctive.
- I feel like you're not gonna blend in
if you're shouting out this ass that every person
you walk past.
- Yeah, and I can't deal with another one of those in my life.
I've accidentally set one up for my upcoming tour.
- I'll have you.
- Yeah, I would.
So I've set up a code word, which is,
if you see me in the street, you see me at the gig or whatever,
and you yell, "Hey, dick face!"
Then you're gonna get a special bit of merch that I've created.
- But how do you stop it from just being a random person
who shall stick face that you were in the street?
- Have you really done that?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- And you've incentivized people to show,
"Hey, dick face that you were in the street."
- It was to do with an anecdote about what my son called me.
And so it was sort of a that I mentioned it.
As part of my other week of we were at this show,
I said, "I'm on tour and this is what you need to say."
- I think even though it was part of an anecdote,
I think you could have chosen something else.
- It was an emotional final episode, and I just said it,
and then when it went out, I realized my mistake,
and that's my life now.
So I can't have no, "Hey, this ass eats dick face."
(laughing)
Yeah, that's, that can't be my life.
- I think that's gilding the lily a bit.
- Can't be my life.
Has that happened yet?
- No, 'cause the tour starts in October, so I've got, you know,
I'm waiting for it to happen.
- On tour days that you're having a stuff out, so it's not just
in the street.
I mean, if you listen to this or watching "C" down in the street,
feel free to shout it, but you just might not get
the free much.
- No, yeah, exactly.
- That's fair.
- Yeah.
- Well, thank you, James, for a great suggestion.
- I do like the idea of a code word.
That is cool.
- Yeah, really good.
- We've got something.
- Right.
- Three more pages of names.
- We've got a live show tonight.
(laughing)
- What time is it?
- It's, we've barely been going any time at all.
- Cool.
- A vlog until we're actually on the stage.
- Two hours.
- Okay.
- And we've got an hour and a half more of this.
(laughing)
- And a cab journey.
- No, look, Brian, Brian Loophole,
well, I should say, I don't approve of people coming up
with silly names of themselves, but Brian Loophole
has written in with the suggestion for the book title.
- Okay.
- The book of things named after someone when you think,
"I don't need to say, okay."
Didn't Dan work in a blog for his tour very well there?
- Yeah, I thought so.
- That was so natural.
- It just, it flowed over me.
I almost didn't notice, oh, Dan's blogging the tour.
- Well, I didn't say the title, this changes everything,
and I didn't say it was October and November.
- And you don't think you mentioned any of the places
you're playing?
- No, I didn't mention Manchester or Leeds or...
- No, any more places.
- Or Cambridge.
- Yep, yeah.
- Any others?
- You did. - Adam Bro.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Did you mention Bristol?
- Bristol, didn't mention that.
I'm not shameless.
- Did you mention whether or not tickets are reasonably priced?
- I like 20 quid.
- It's so nice.
- Small rooms, it's gonna be incredible.
- It's a bargain.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- So I didn't do any of that.
- And that was good.
- Well done, Dick Face.
(laughing)
- You're merch.
- So Brian Loophole writes in,
so he just wanted to suggest a name for Andy's book.
It could be called "I drew a Dislogical Conclusion."
There should be a comment after "I drew"
because that's just a nickname for Andy.
- Oh, yeah.
- And then the Dislogical Conclusion
is actually not because it's not logical, I-illogical,
but because it dislodges your previous conception
of why something was called that.
Therefore, the book is not named
for the reason that you thought it was.
- Yeah.
- So the name of the book, Brian says is,
"I come a drew colon a Dislogical Conclusion."
I hope that puts the message to rest.
- I do as well.
(laughing)
- That's good.
What do you think?
- Of course that's the name of the book.
- Great.
- "I drew a Dislogical Conclusion."
- And then so we've solved it.
That's wonderful.
- Yeah, great.
- I've been working away on it as you're about to hear.
♪ It's T-T-A-U-M-A-A ♪
♪ P-R-T-A-F-O-Q-U-E ♪
♪ Things that are unexpectedly named after a person
rather than a functional quality. ♪
♪ Unexpected eponyms, N-S-T-A-A-F-F-F ♪
- No, we've had a lot of beef breaking out.
A bit of spicy meat, in fact,
over who came up with the concept in the first place.
- Someone wrote in, didn't they?
And they said, "I was the first one to do it,
and it makes me smile every time you do it."
- Saying you were the first one to do it, James.
Saying you James, there was a place called Snowflake
in Arizona.
- Oh, okay.
- Arastas Snow and Mr. Flake.
And yes, that's what Emma Gurdler points out, ages ago.
Gareth Taylor thinks it was episode 397,
where Anna's fact is about George Lucas,
who lives on the Luke Skywalker.
- Well, the Lucas Valley, his ranch is in the Lucas Valley,
which is named after John Lucas, the 19th century rancher.
So that is an early thing.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Someone else points out,
Nevin Morgan shares an episode in,
four,
cheers, sorry, I'm getting overexcited.
Shares the story in episode 30,
the story of Ryanair's name.
James says, "Ryanair is named not for Christopher Ryan,
but the less famous co-founder Tony Ryan."
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- In this episode, James is ever so amused by this story.
Flash forward a few years,
and here's the logic to them, what happened?
- I think repetition, it's just Nevin.
- It's just Nevin.
- Yeah, like, I think that's a fairly obvious answer.
But Catherine Tark has maybe the earliest of all,
this could be Patient Zero, episode 28.
- Oh, that's early.
- Dan, we're talking about Dom Perignon,
and named after Dom Perignon, a monk.
And Nat Cho's being named after Ignacio.
- Yeah, somebody.
Could that be the earliest?
Crucially, you don't say, "Oh, that could be a book."
- Well, this is, yeah, it's a format of fact
that we've been doing a long time,
but who said this is a book to begin with?
- I think me, I'm not sure.
But this is all because of Dave Rool,
who wrote into the inbox all that time ago.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I'm nilly a year ago now, I'm just.
(laughing)
- Would you guys be interested in me knocking the book together?
- Yeah.
- As a freebie for some tier or some, like, a giveaway,
or as an e-book, I don't think we should,
I think any tree should die for this.
(laughing)
- I do.
- I'm very, I mean, now that we've got such a hot title.
- Absolutely.
- In true, it's logical conclusion.
- Like, again, like I said this before,
but I just think the joke runs very thin, very quickly.
- Yeah, I think, you know how,
oh, you remember how you can see where people stop reading
on Kindle, because you can see how many pages,
and like, in a brief history of time,
people get 4% of the way in.
I don't think this is gonna have the sticking power
of a brief history of time.
I think this is gonna be a one or two percent.
- Right.
- In fact, that makes my job much easier,
'cause I could just make that bit good in the full knowledge.
- I think we said in the last drop as a line
that the second half of the book,
where you put the dress,
it's gonna be a lot longer than the first half of the book.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
- But yeah, look, I mean, whatever keeps you happy
and he makes me happy.
So if you want to make the book,
I think you go for it.
- Well, it's gonna be a big task.
Like, I want to, I want to,
I'll be not doing my work properly on the main show.
- Well, I won't be curating drop as a line
as carefully while I'm writing it.
So I hope.
- Why is this show the thing that is gonna suffer
when you already write other books?
Why isn't that other books?
What's gonna suffer?
Surely you should just not write another novel
for a year and write this step?
- Well, a lot of people would be writing to me
asking me to not watch that problem.
My editor, my agent, all sorts.
I suppose, no, you're right.
I suppose I should cut down on the other books.
I'll write to them and say,
"I'm sorry, there's not going to be a sequel to "Bad Deeds,"
which has just been released in "Hardback."
- You didn't do that nearly as quickly as that.
- Please stand in it.
- Clang!
- That was awful.
- You made the mistake of saying its name.
- I know.
Well, that's a shame, yeah, yeah.
Okay, well, anyway.
- I have a new one.
- I saw on Instagram.
- Everything happens so much.
- Coming out later this year.
- Yeah, yeah, that's actually the title of it.
That's actually, they actually let me make that the title.
- We've all now got a book with the word
"Everything in the title."
- "Everything to playful."
- Uh-huh.
- "Fear of everything else."
- "Everything happens so much."
- "Let's do a bundle."
- "Let's do a signing everywhere."
That'd be funny.
- That's very funny.
- You know, 'cause they will have everything in the title.
So we can do a signing in like,
everywhere in the world.
- All at once.
- "Everything ever or ever."
- It's perfect.
- It's like some of my already have that title.
(laughing)
- All right, look, we better wrap it up.
(upbeat music)
Thank you so much, everyone, for watching
or listening to this episode of "Droppers Align."
If you've enjoyed it, why not be part of the next one?
By emailing your comments, queries,
your extreme fishes, your get us off the hooks,
your arm actuallys, to your spicy meat.
We haven't had any spicy meat for a long time.
- Now, semen squabbles, where have they gone?
- Squabbles.
- Row, row, row, brackets, your boat closed brackets.
Same as semen squabbles.
Your old fish.
Your thanks, but no thanks is.
Your secret squid, is there any more?
- I'd usually say bye to us for that.
- Oh, I'm so sorry, guys, bye.
- That's all right.
- That's okay.
- I hope you had a good time.
- Bye to you.
- Thank you.
- And thank you, Andy.
You're welcome.
I do it even without thanks.
- That's good, and now we're gonna go as flesh your head
down the side like, (laughing)
bye.
(upbeat music)